megacams.me 2017-01-19

# Privacy Policy - Megacams

### PERSONAL INFORMATION

We only collect personal information from visitors to our web site when they voluntarily provide it to us by completing our registration form or electing to use one of our services. We may require visitors to provide us with information including, but not limited to, their name, physical address, email address, birth date, credit card expiration date, username, password, and on occasion a unique identifier (such as their mother's maiden name).

### NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION

When visitors access our web site, certain non-personal information may be collected from them including, but not limited to, their browser type (e.g., FireFox or Internet Explorer), operating system (e.g., Windows or Macintosh), IP address, and the domain name from which they accessed the site (e.g. google.com). In addition, we may collect information about visitors' browsing behavior, such as the date and time they visit the web site, the areas or pages of our web site that they visit, the amount of time spent viewing the site, the number of times the visitor returns to the site, and click-stream data. We do not track any information about visitors once they leave our site. We may use cookies (small text files that are stored on visitors computers when they access our web site) to collect this information. Information collected through cookies may be combined with visitors' personal information. We may also allow unaffiliated third parties, such as advertisers, to serve cookies to visitors of our web site. Visitors are always free to decline cookies, but in doing so they may not be able to use certain features on our web site. The "help" segment of the toolbar on most browsers explains how to configure a browser to not accept new cookies, how to have the browser inform a user when they receive a new cookie, and how to erase cookies from their hard drives.

### IN WHAT WAY DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL AND NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION?

Our goal in collecting personal information is to provide visitors with the most personalized web experience possible and our advertisers with an efficient means to reach the right audience. By knowing a little about our visitors, we are able to deliver more relevant content and advertisements, and provide better services. We may use information collected from visitors to our web site for any of the following purposes: (1) to send visitors information and promotional materials about our company, (2) to send visitors information and promotional materials from our marketing partners and third parties (such as advertisers on our web site), (3) to deliver targeted display advertisements and offers by email (by matching criteria provided by our advertisers with information collected from our visitors), (4) to contact visitors to our web site when necessary, (5) to allow one-click purchases or access to proprietary content by pre-populating fields, within registration or other transaction screens, with a visitor's name, billing address, and credit or charge card information (among other things), as provided by that visitor, (6) to help diagnose problems with our server, (7) to administer our web site, (8) to conduct internal reviews of our site (e.g., to determine the number of visitors to the site), (9) to help us better understand visitors' use of our site, and (10) to protect the security or integrity of our site. Non-personal information will be used for purposes of conducting internal reviews of the site, monitoring the site, and providing a greater online experience for our visitors.

### DO WE DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION?

As a rule, we do not share or otherwise distribute our Subscribers' personal information, including email addresses (i.e. we do not share, sell, or distribute our email lists to third parties). We may transfer or disclose information collected from visitors to our web site to our employees and independent contractors, to our parent company, subsidiaries and affiliates, and to our consultants, other business associates, and suppliers, if the disclosure will enable that party to perform a business, professional, or technical support function for us, or if required to do so by law.

### WHAT SECURITY MEASURES DO WE TAKE TO PROTECT YOUR DATA?

To help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data integrity, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place certain physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect from visitors to our web site. We use SSL (Secure Socket Layer) technology to protect any credit card information you provide us. We allow access to personal information only to persons and entities engaging in activities provided for by this Privacy Policy. Visitors should consider any communication that they transmit to us (such as data, questions or answers, comments, suggestions, or communications submitted to a chat room) to be non-confidential. We will not be liable or responsible if information that belongs to a visitor is intercepted and used by an unintended recipient.

### WE PROTECT CHILDREN'S PRIVACY

Protecting the privacy of children is VERY important to us. For that reason we do not structure any part of our site to attract anyone under the age of 18 (21 in some areas) and we do not allow anyone under the age of 18 (21 in some areas) to register and become a member of our site.

### CORPORATE CHANGES

In the event of a merger, acquisition, asset or stock sale, bankruptcy, or other asset transfer (regardless of legal formality), any of our assets may be transferred to a third party, including personal information collected from visitors to our web site.

### ACCEPTANCE OF PRIVACY TERMS & CONDITIONS

By visiting this web site, you are agreeing to the practices described in this Privacy Policy. By visiting this site, you also accept, without limitation or qualification, all terms and conditions concerning the use of this site. We may at any time revise these terms and conditions. You are bound by any such revisions and should therefore periodically visit this page to review the then-current terms and conditions to which you are bound. To the extent that any of the third-party sites accessible through our web site (such as our advertisers) have different privacy practices from those stated in this Privacy Policy, those third-party privacy practices govern the collection and use of information you provide when visiting those sites. We are not responsible for the policies, content, and practices of other companies.

### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

There may be times when we need to change the terms of this Privacy Policy. To ensure that you are aware of our current privacy practices, please bookmark this page and check back often.

### HOW CAN YOU ACCESS THE INFORMATION WE HAVE COLLECTED FROM YOU?

Visitors who wish to access or change the information they provided to our web site, should visit the Customer Service section of this site and contact us via Email.

### ARE IMAGES BY FACE RECOGNITION STORED BY YOU?

We store the images for 24 hours, after that they will be deleted. The images are no files on disk but a binary string in our database. Images you upload are only accessible by your unique url and this url expires after 24 hours and the image will be removed.

### 3th party image processing

The image you upload will be processed by Microsoft cognitive service. These images will be processed in the united states of america or worldwide.
